{
    "id": "1c74c717ada843e895e9a321188f449c",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He accused me …………………….. stealing his money.",
            "description": "We accuse somebody of something",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f4e2b78528d4276ac2747df211d0a32"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am afraid ………………………… spiders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14f3de207ad7406a955a313027218cdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you agree …………………………… his decision to quit?",
            "description": "You agree with a person, opinion or policy.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24104e298fd04050a6165de6cf42defa"
        },
        {
            "question": "We agree …………………………. most things.",
            "description": "We agree about a subject of discussion.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f2226b9debaf4be69b4421ae90c4c193"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know why he is angry ………………………….. me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c293b8add0314a32b0418865e6aed44a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am anxious ……………………………. my exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17297705083941a08470cba2fa6af93d"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all anxious ………………………….. an end to this conflict.",
            "description": "Anxious for means eager to have.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0d8707a11ae64ab58fce146c53997a59"
        },
        {
            "question": "They apologized …………………………… the old lady.",
            "description": "Apologize to somebody for something",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e4df2727cb124f0d9dd16a00e17e73f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrived …………………………….. New York in the afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e63cd888920447495c28e69ccd619d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite good …………………………… mind reading.",
            "description": "We say good at or bad at. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6cef8ccad00b464485decae763812e75"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe …………………………. ghosts or fairies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46c1a9a6be7c450f9688c101737499fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those vases belong ………………………………. that shelf.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "da5bbe8810e44746a708d3aa9efe6405"
        }
    ]
}